{
    "id": "6e5652bc07e64ed7ac0695efbaf83f46",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. the footsteps, the thief ran away.",
            "description": "The present participle is used to combine two clauses when they refer to actions that happen simultaneously. ",
            "answers": [
                "Hearing",
                "Having heard",
                "Heard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d5dbfce361764bd2837c8134f0a9a374"
        },
        {
            "question": "The poor man ……………………. very hungry ate the food greedily.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been",
                "being",
                "having"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d53359cf48e64b828599a5f067011706"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. his muscle power, he was defeated by his opponent.",
            "description": "In spite of is a preposition. Use it before a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c2dac4ced4154856a2169cf2faabc99a"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………. a cripple, he cannot walk.",
            "description": "He is a cripple. He cannot walk. Here we can replace is with being and write 'Being a cripple, he cannot walk.'",
            "answers": [
                "Being",
                "Been",
                "Having"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7949c34843894b16b5d316bfaec725c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. himself in deep debt, he decided to sell his home.",
            "description": "He found himself in deep debt. He decided to sell his home. We can connect these two sentences using finding. ",
            "answers": [
                "Finding",
                "Found",
                "Being"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "17d62f87ef414d56b720cc9c2e8eb4a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the event of such a thing ………………………, I will quit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "happening",
                "happens",
                "happened"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "78addacec9f64161a783c918cad23b16"
        },
        {
            "question": "He intends to make another attempt ……………………….. his repeated failures.",
            "description": "Either despite or notwithstanding can be used here. ",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "notwithstanding",
                "nonetheless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f67ac8cc19004f948a219a528835be27"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. my best efforts, I could not succeed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Despite",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "93550817973a42dc816ee8290fac3663"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………. pity for the mouse, the magician turned it into a cat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Feeling",
                "Felt",
                "Being"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "57ff0f8e1e9f448aa040809d353609d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. dissatisfied, he resigned his job.",
            "description": "He was dissatisfied. He resigned his job. We can replace was with being. Being dissatisfied, he resigned his job.",
            "answers": [
                "Having",
                "Being",
                "Been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d74e75b143d4b0c99d670be33ba396c"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. the message, he departed.",
            "description": "When one action follows another action, we can express that idea with a perfect participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "Delivering",
                "Being delivering",
                "Having delivered"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2226ccbc75314af0865c4036b3a6bdc9"
        }
    ]
}